Sam Peterson

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+11 230 909 8298

peter2020@fakemail

30 Rockefeller Plaza, NewYork, NY

EDUCATION

University of Kwazulu-Natal *Bachelor of Computer Science and Information Technlogies*

July 2015 - Nov 2017

University of Kwazulu-Natal

Bachelor of Computer Science Honours

November 2018 - Present

SKILL

Wordpress, Joomla HTML5, CSS, JS Adobe Photoshop Sketch

ABOUT ME

Results driven individual with four years experience desiring to bring engineering and telecommunication experience to a software engineering position at ABC Company. Searching for the oppotunirt to bring 8+ years experience, and server maintenance to a software engineer position with ABC Company incorporating critical thinking, problem solving and leadership

EXPERIENCE

BACK-END DEVELOPER

Google Inc

January 2017 - August 2017

- Facilitate back-end aspect of things
- Make sure everything was in sync with everything
- Communicate well with the front end stuff
- Make sure data storage and app is in sync

TESTER

Microsoft

June 2019 - Present

- Maintain server
 - Provide and facilitate end user assistance
 - Maintain computer paraphernalia
- Make sure data storage and app is in sync

REFERENCE

Kutlo Sek, Google Inc

Senior Developer

Email: kutlosek@fakeemail.com

Annah Navaro, CNN Television

CNN Correspondent
Email: annah@cnn.com